# Jennifer Quintal

## Full Stack Developer

#### **Profile**

I'm a full-stack web developer experienced in operations and experiential marketing. With a passion for following market trends, and building vendor relationships, I have a proven passion for implementing strategic initiatives, creating and developing products to fulfil client needs

### **Projects**

**Route Roamer,** an application where users can create an AI-generated, personalized travel itinerary for anywhere around the world and suggested activities will appear on Google Maps & Apr 2023

• Tech Stack: React, Next, ChatGPT API, Google Maps API, Mapbox API, PostgreSQL

**Jungle**, a mini e-commerce application where users can view and purchase products in a secure environment using the Stripe API. & Apr 2023

• Tech Stack: Ruby, Rails, Stripe API, PostgreSQL

JNMaps - WikiMap, an application where using Google Maps API, users can create, view and modify maps &

Mar 2023

• Tech Stack: Node, Express, Sass, Google Maps

**Scheduler,** React based application to book interview appointments between students and mentors &

Mar 2023

Tech Stack: React, Axios, Storybook, Cypress

**Tweeter,** a single-page Twitter clone where users can compose a 140 character tweet ≥ Mar 2023

• Tech Stack: HTML, CSS, JS, jQuery, AJAX, Node and Express

#### Skills

Languages (JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SQL, Ruby), Frameworks & Libraries (NodeJS, React, Next.js, Ajax, Express, EJS, jQuery, Bootstrap, Rails), Systems & Databases (PostgreSQL, Git), **Testing** (Jest, Storybook, Cypress, RSpec), Additional Skills (Microsoft Office, SalesForce, Softrip, Negotiations, Budgets & Reporting, Communication & Presenting, Leadership)

#### **Education**

#### Lighthouse Labs,

Diploma: Full-Stack Web Development 2023 | Vancouver

**York University,** Bachelor of Arts: English 2013 - 2016 | Toronto

Concordia University, Major: Joint Specialization in Anthropology & Sociology Minor: English Literature

2011 - 2013 | Montreal

#### **Employment**

## Polar Client Experience Advisor,

**Quark Expeditions** 

Nov 2021 - Nov 2022 | Remote

- Modified client accounts to support their needs
- Liaise between clients and Sales team

## **Senior Operations Coordinator,**

WorldStrides Explorica

Oct 2018 - Sep 2020 | Toronto

- Acting manager for 6 months, managing a team of four
- · Created and developed new initiatives and products
- Collaborated with various senior stakeholders
- Negotiating and contracting competitive rates
- Analyzed reporting and operational stats to ensure goals are being met and surpassed